protecting your family is your number
one priority
icici lombard presents the perfect plan
for you
the family shield plan is comprehensive
flexible unique it covers more to
protect more
some of the key features of this plan
are
infectious disease benefit
personal accident benefit flexibility
family policy discount
tenure and renewal discount the
infectious disease benefit can be very
helpful as various illnesses have become
more common now it provides for coverage
against specific vector-borne diseases
rabies and tetanus
gastrointestinal infections
viral and nervous infections
personal accident benefit is a key
factor for protection
it covers death and disabilities
adventure sports
broken bones and children's education
grant
this plan offers you what you need you
can opt for any one or more base
benefits under one or more sections you
will be eligible for the base benefits
and or extensions if premium has been
paid what's more multiple airground
covers to choose from are available too
this plan offers you a tenure and
renewal discount too
you can get a policy term of up to three
years with long term discount
you also get a five percent renewal
discount the renewable premium must be
paid on or before the policy expiry date
or within 30 days
that's not all
you get a family policy discount of up
to 7.5 percent too
give your family the protection they
deserve and give yourself a hassle-free
claim experience too
with icici lombard's family shield plan
you are our priority